Hello and welcome back to the new video open,
so I got a comment from a brother, he
says that brother, the front
left panel of my car is completely
damaged, this panel on the left side of the front panel,
you can see here, there
is a joint here, this panel, from
here this entire panel
comes as a complete panel, he is asking me that first
of all what will be its cost, secondly, if
I get it painted from Honda's service
center i.e. showroom, then what will be its cost, I
want to give you the total information,
first of all, if you get this panel changed, then
your panel, I think, will cost
112 to 1500 per piece, I think
one piece will cost you ₹1200, the casting of this panel will be
your total cost for painting it,
if you get it painted from the authorized dealership, then the
price of its paint will be a little expensive there,
but if you
get it done after market, then it will be less, then you will get it a little
less, but if  If
I talk about the cost of the panel paint, which if
you get done from an authorized service center, then
its cost will be around 800 to 1000
rupees, but if you get it done from an
aftermarket, then it is
possible that you can get this aftermarket paint done for 500 to 600 rupees.
Thirdly,
if you want to get the total body of the vehicle
painted, then its
total cost will be 5000 rupees. I
also felt good after talking to people in my city
and my friends who do not live outside, that is, in Shahdol, they
all said that the cost
of my vehicle is
49485200, that is, 5000 rupees. The cost of getting the
total body painted is the same for everyone. So, hope
you will be satisfied with the information.